<meta xmlns="http://exist-db.org/xquery/repo">
    <config>
        <!-- App title -->
        <title>Literature in Context</title>
        <!-- App description -->
        <description>This is the working space for Literature in Context, an XML project that seeks to provide open-access, reliably-sourced, and collaboratively-constructed annotated editions of British and American literature of the long 18th century for classroom use. This project is funded by the National Endowment for the Humanities and developed by faculty at The University of Virginia and Marymount University.</description>
        <!-- Contact email -->
        <contact/>
        <!-- Logo name (assumes path to logo is $app-root/resources/img/) -->
        <logo/>
        <!-- Web Site URL -->
        <url/>
        <!-- Root of app for building dynamic links. Default is eXist app root -->
        <nav-base/>
        <!-- eXist app root for app deployment-->
        <app-root>LiC</app-root>
        <!-- eXist data app root for gazetteer data -->
        <data-root>LiC-data</data-root>
        <!-- Root path where page images stored -->
        <!-- Example, swap in github repository: https://github.com/tonyahowe/LiC/raw/master/ -->
        <page-images-root>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tonyahowe/LiC/master/</page-images-root>
        <!-- How HTML/PDF/EPUB will be generated. POC uses a simple TEI xquery for expediency. -->
        <!-- Allow XSLT plugin: /resources/xslt/html/html.xsl -->
        <work-html-transformation type="xquery"/>
        <work-pdf-transformation type="xquery"/>
        <work-epub-transformation type="xquery"/>
        <!--NOTE: may not need this for LiC. Base URI for identifiers in app data -->
        <base_uri/>
        <!-- NOTE: may not need this for LiC. xpath to unique identifier for record, syriaca.org uses tei:idno[@type='URL'], this is the default value -->
        <id-path/>
        <featured>
            <slide type="text" imageURL="" imageDesc="" order="1">
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-4">
                        <img src="resources/images/Wheatley.jpg" alt="Image of Philis Wheatley."/>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-md-8">
                        <p><em>Literature in Context: An Open Anthology of Literature, 1660-1830</em>, is a web-accessible and mobile-friendly digital anthology of curated, contextualized, machine-readable literature in English designed for use by students, teachers, and the general public. Because we anticipate these pieces being used in the classroom, it is essential that the material be authoritative, citable, and printable--therefore, users can create custom coursepacks that live both online and in print.</p>
                        <p>At once an Open Educational Resource and a digital humanities project that seeks to bring to life the literature of the long eighteenth century, <em>Literature in Context</em> also provides resources to help instructors at the college level engage students in the task of editing and annotating literary texts that can be added to the collection. By including students in the production of the anthology, the project will foreground how the public construction of knowledge is essential to understanding the modern world.</p>
                        <p>Sponsored by funding from the National Endowment for the Humanities, and led by teams of scholars, students, and librarians at Marymount University and the University of Virginia, our goal is a platform for establishing authoritative, contextualized works that teachers and students can use with confidence. In this way, we hope to provide a tool for the thoughtful, collaborative editing and dissemination of our shared humanistic heritage.</p>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </slide>
            <slide type="work" id="/work/Behn/behn-rover" imageURL="/resources/images/Behn.jpg" imageDesc="" order="2"/>
            <slide type="text" imageURL="" imageDesc="" order="4">
                <div class="row">
                      <h2>Coursepacks</h2>
                      <p>As a born-digital platform crafted with the needs of the classroom in mind, <em>Literature in Context</em> offers teachers the ability to create custom mini-anthologies or coursepacks with ease. They can be housed online for persistent digital access, but also formatted for printing and simplicity of citation. In later build-outs, <em>Literature in Context</em> will enable multiple skins that enable a variety of reading experiences, and we also plan to incorporate annotation tools like hypothes.is to make collaborative reading possible. </p>
                </div>
            </slide>
            <slide type="text" imageURL="" imageDesc="" order="4">
                <div class="row">
                      <h2>Get in touch!</h2>
                      <p><img alt="twitter" style="border-width:0" src="$nav-base/resources/images/twitter.png" class="social-media"/></p>
                      <p><img alt="github" style="border-width:0" src="$nav-base/resources/images/github.png" class="social-media"/></p>
                      <p><img alt="email" style="border-width:0" src="$nav-base/resources/images/email.png" class="social-media"/></p>
                      As a born-digital platform crafted with the needs of the classroom in mind, <em>Literature in Context</em> offers teachers the ability to create custom mini-anthologies or coursepacks with ease. They can be housed online for persistent digital access, but also formatted for printing and simplicity of citation. In later build-outs, <em>Literature in Context</em> will enable multiple skins that enable a variety of reading experiences, and we also plan to incorporate annotation tools like hypothes.is to make collaborative reading possible. </p>
                </div>
            </slide>
            <!-- <slide type="recentWork" imageURL="/resources/images/Behn.jpg" imageDesc="" order="2"/> -->
            <!--<slide type="coursepack" id="Poems2" imageURL="/resources/images/Equiano.jpg" imageDesc="" order="4"/>-->
        </featured>
    </config>
</meta>
